Proceed to Pompeii.
I have hidden a key somewhere
near the Cave Cana mosaic.
This hidden key will operate
the vehicle that'll allow
your team safe passage as you deliver
my daughter. Fugo! Abbacchio! Giorno!
You three will travel to
Pompeii to secure that key.
Thank you.
In my life, I won't be able to fight.
I'll continue to fight!
I will be
able to fight.
Fighting God?
Pompeii, ancient Roman resort
and city of culture and vitality.
When Mount Vesuvius erupted back in AD 79,
the city was ravaged by
fire and buried by ash.
It was a catastrophe.
Later, archaeologists discovered
a metropolis frozen in time.
Everything there was preserved.
Entire villas, wine bottles,
roads, even carriage tracks.
So you're aware,
the Cave Canem is a mosaic
of a dog located in the
vestibule of the so-called
House of the Tragic Poet.
Oh, Fugo.
It seems we needed to turn
right back there, not left.
Isn't it a little bit late
to be telling me that?
Tell me, what good does it do to
inform me of a turn after the fact?
You're absolutely right. I'm sorry.
Next time, I will.
Did I say anything about
next time, new kid?
I'm talking about now!
Check your emotions.
We're in a hurry, so calm down.
You don't think I know that?
It's annoying as shit,
but this is typical Fugo.
What's really bugging me is this
new recruit, Giorno Giovanna.
Uttarati wants us to treat him as one
of our own, so I'll do what I must.
But there's something about this
guy, something I can't get past.
Eventually, he's going to screw up big
time, and his blunder could get us killed.
Good old Pompei.
I haven't set foot
there since I was a kid.
Abacchio, Giorno, let's hustle.
Our destination is about
a hundred meters ahead.
It should take thirty minutes or so to get
what we need and hightail it back to camp!
Abbacchio, Giorno, eyes up.
Well, that didn't take long.
How many?
Just one.
At least for the moment.
He's watching us from behind that pillar.
And by that pillar, which
one do you mean exactly?
Open your damn eyes, Giorno.
There's only one pillar here.
You can't see it from there?
Fugo, you're definitely
right about the pillar.
But there's no one watching us.
I know what I'm looking at, damn it!
He's closing in!
Fugo! Right there!
He's sauntering this way!
I know I saw him.
A guy just came out
from behind that pillar.
I saw his every move with this mirror.
What the hell?
There he is! Look there! He came out!
Wait, is he skulking in the mirror?
He showed his stand!
One of you attacked!
Hey, take a beat!
Nothing you've said in the last
few minutes has made any sense!
Wait, is something the
matter with the mirror?
Shit!
He's coming in for the kill!
You have to get away from the mirror!
What? Giorno! Abokyo!
Where are you?
What's going on?
Where'd you go?
That mirror freak vanished, too.
What'd he do?
Of course the creepy hanging
mirror was a red flag.
How the hell did I fall for that?
What is this guy's stand?
How does it work?
Also, I don't know what it is, but...
Something about this place
just doesn't look right.
Xiao!
What?
Panna Code Fugo M.
Your IQ is 152, and you entered
university at the age of 13.
But a certain professor
rubbed you the wrong way,
so you decided to beat him to a
bloody pulp with an encyclopedia.
Frankly, the rest is a
depressing biography.
You're currently traveling with
the failed cop, Leone Abacchio,
as well as the lack of
data must mean he's new.
I believe you called him Giorno.
You bastard.
Tell me where they are.
Out with it.
Where did you put them?
Tell me now!
My watch is backwards.
And now it's on my right wrist,
which doesn't make any sense.
I get it. Damn you.
So that's what your stand does.
I knew you were quick,
but that was impressive.
I like your eagerness, Fugo.
I'll admit that I wasn't aiming for you,
but since you noticed the
mirror before the others,
you get to go first.
Abbacchio and Giorno didn't disappear.
This is some kind of mirror world.
I'm the victim here.
He dragged me into his
own little playground.
Fugo!
Come out already!
Giorno, didn't you see
anything suspicious?
Not sure.
One second I'm looking at
him, the next he's gone.
Fugo, where are you?
Right before he vanished, he warned
us to get away from the mirror.
He asked if we could see the man
walking from behind the pillar.
This mirror.
Strano.
Something's off about this mirror.
But what?
Now for the question at hand.
Where did you and your comrades
hide the boss's daughter?
Actually, I should say that's
the more important question.
My other question concerns why you goons
are snooping around the city of death.
That's the piece of this puzzle
I just can't seem to ignore.
It doesn't take a genius to figure out
you came here searching for something.
Whatever it is,
it would have to be vital to protecting
the girl to justify coming all this way,
right?
Just around that corner, you'll
find the famous Cave Cana mosaic.
Is that where your prize lies?
Well, whatever it is, I'm taking it!
Now do yourself a favor and tell
me what this thing is, Fugo!
Eat shit!
So you choose death, then!
Wrong, Stranzo!
That honor will go to you once
I unleash my stand's power!
Purple smoke!
It won't manifest. Why? I see.
Purple smoke, eh?
It's an interesting name
for your no-show ability.
I'm absolutely sure I
brought out my stand.
I can even feel its power.
So where the hell is it?
Hey, Giorno, I need you
to walk toward me slowly.
You need me to what?
Get your newbie ass over here!
We're running out of time!
Move it now!
What?
Are we being attacked?
No, kid!
Stand down now!
That's not the enemy!
It's Fugo's stand!
Unless you want to die, quick
digging around and get back!
Fugos, move away from purple smoke!
Hurry, fool!
I suppose I should tell
you you're inside a mirror.
Do you know why I pulled you
in here all by your lonesome?
Hint, it's not for the peace and quiet.
It's cause bringing
along any of your fellow
combatants could put my
own safety in jeopardy.
and I just can't have that.
I control everything here.
That is my unique talent.
All you see before you is
devoid of life, fully inanimate.
We're the only living
things in this realm.
I made it a point to
keep everything else out.
I permitted your entry
because my plan needed you.
You catching on?
Your stand manifested on the
other side of the mirror!
Now feast your eyes upon my mirror man!
Purple smoke materialized on the outside.
This is a nightmare, but there's
got to be a way I can fight back!
Panacota Fugo was born
into tremendous wealth
and lived on a vast estate outside Napoli.
He was blessed, not only with
a life of luxury and privilege,
but with a great intellect as well.
To many, he lived the perfect
life, devoid of any hardship.
But what the public didn't see were the
many expectations placed
on Fugo's shoulders.
The pressure from them was
crushing his spirit day by day.
At times, Fugo suffered bouts of inexplicable
rage, which caused him to act out.
It was a deep anger that took
all his might to contain.
At the age of just 13,
he began university.
It was there that his near-uncontrollable
furor erupted into tragedy.
Fugo.
Oh, Professor.
Now what could you be up
to at this ungodly hour?
It's for our assignment.
I can't find the judicial precedent.
Oh don't be silly you
know that you can always
come to me with anything hard that arises.
No I wouldn't want to
trouble you if I don't
have to guiding gifted
young men like you is.
No trouble at all it's
my scholarly duty how
about it have dinner at
my place and I'll teach.
You a few things I have
to go now wait just a
moment I'd be more than
happy to loose my lips.
regarding the questions
on the next big test.
Everything's going to be just fine.
Stop it.
Relax, you're in good hands.
Get your hands off me!
I looked up to you!
I wanted to be like you!
You disgusting piece of shit!
I heard Profissori's
getting real cozy with Fugo.
You sure Fugo didn't bait the hook?
That would explain how he
got into a school like this.
Fugo's parents leveraged their wealth
to ensure all charges were dropped.
But they no longer treated him like a son,
and he was no longer part of the family.
Without support, Fugo turned to
shoplifting and pickpocketing for survival.
In an ironic twist of fate,
it was his new way of life that
would make full use of his intellect.
Did you think you could just
run away without paying?
I'll make sure you rot in jail.
Sorry, but you will never be
able to put me behind bars.
I take it you're not
familiar with De Seiko vs.
Argento, 1982?
Based on the results of that case,
it is highly likely that the court will
determine I acted out of basic necessity.
Bucciarati, please, you have to
do something about this child!
Hmm.
How interesting.
Fugo's visit happened to
occur right as Bucciarati
was pondering the
formation of his own team.
There.
Now you basically know
everything about me.
You can stop feeling sorry for me.
I'm not unhappy if that helps.
I see. Hmm.
I don't think you're here today by chance.
Would you join my team, Panakata Fugo?
Your intellect is one of a kind.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I've got nothing against becoming a
mafioso, but I've made up my mind.
It's for the best if I go it
alone in life. Oh? Why's that?
I told you.
When I lose my temper, my
darkest thoughts take over.
If I acquiesced and
joined up with your team,
I couldn't guarantee I wouldn't kill you.
Well, lucky for you, I'm
willing to bet on those odds.
Leave your past and come with me.
I swear you and your
talents will be respected.
I want you here, demons and all.
His words stirred Fugo's soul.
Soon after, Fugo would undergo Pulpo's
test and would acquire Purple Smoke.
So this is Fugo's stand.
Fugo's nowhere to be seen,
but somehow his stand is here.
He materialized his stand,
which means he's alive.
At least for now.
Dammit, where the hell did he go?
How is he going to protect himself?
Get back, Giorno.
You're still too close.
Fugo almost never manifests his stand,
unless he's totally out of options.
He's more than likely fighting
for his life right this second.
I told you to get back!
He seems more concerned about that stand
than finding out where Fugo's been taken.
It's like he feels threatened.
Why would it be lashing
out all of a sudden?
This isn't good.
We have to retreat.
Come on, run!
You're not making any sense.
Something's in that mirror.
We have to find Fugo.
Until we know exactly where
he is, nothing else matters.
I'm really getting tired of
that mouth of yours, pissant.
You're an annoying brown noser,
but I thought I'd be nice and
give the poor newbie a heads up.
It's attacking.
Giorno, get moving!
Interesting.
So you activated your
stand outside the mirror.
Oh well, that doesn't change a thing!
It really doesn't matter what
kind of tricks your stand can do.
Nothing it does will
have any effect on me.
I, on the other hand, will make you my
punching bag and finish you at my leisure!
Huh? A crow?
But why'd it fall out of the sky?
It died.
But how come? Stay back.
When purple smoke starts
swinging its fists,
you better hope you're
as far away as possible.
What is up with all these dead animals?
It's a lethal virus.
That's the power of Fugo's stand.
It's a ghastly ability.
How is that possible?
Take a look at its hands.
When its fists strike
something, the capsules shatter,
spewing the infectious
agent contained inside?
into the air.
Once airborne,
the virus infiltrates the body through
respiration or contact with the skin.
It then multiplies violently.
Viral pathogenesis sets
in, and then, death.
Once the virus begins to spread,
any living organism is
subject to its devastating
effects like those crows
your body's metabolic
functions will fail as you
decompose from the inside
out along with your stand
and would you happen to
know its range five meters
since he can still control
his stand he's no farther
than five meters away
that's a good start but
how far does the virus
reach i guess i'm asking
what's the infection radius?
We're safe at this distance.
When the virus is exposed to the elements,
even indoor light can exterminate
it after prolonged exposure.
The sunlight should have those
crows disinfected before too long.
But stay alert.
That beast blasts its victims
with a viral cloud of death,
then melts them into nothingness.
What you're looking at is the
embodiment of Fugo's ferocity.
Uh, what's it doing?
Trying to wipe the drool
off his leg, I think.
That angry grimace is his signature.
He's extremely neurotic.
The slightest bit of grime annoys him.
Every stan's got its
own quirks, I suppose.
Not to be rude, but it doesn't
seem to be very bright.
We're only seeing the manifestation
of his most savage side.
Since that's the case, it stands to
reason Fugo can't see purple smoke at all.
That means he's having
trouble controlling it.
He would never let it
act like that otherwise.
Its body.
What is going on?
The crow looks like it's
diseased or something.
But is it bacterial or viral?
I knew it.
Fugo's lost his grip on his stand.
He's randomly attacking
things in a fit of rage.
No, there's nothing random about this.
There must be something
hidden in that mirror.
He targeted the mirror from the outside.
You're wasting your time, Fugo.
There was nothing special
about the mirror you destroyed.
No matter what your stand tries to do, no
matter what tricks it has up its sleeve...
Mirror Man's World is impenetrable!
Not even viruses can find their way in!
Abacchio, Giorno, you have to understand.
You can't let him drag you
into this Mirror World.
We need to get out of here. Giorno!
Now, Giorno!
We have to go! Move it!
What do you mean?
Move to where?
Surely you don't mean to find the key.
Would you really ditch
Fugo here and let him die?
I strongly suggest watching
your mouth, kid. Listen well.
The mission is to get the key and
safely deliver the girl to the boss.
That's our first priority.
I want to save Fugo as much as you do.
Hell, even more.
But getting that damn key is more
important than our personal feelings.
If it were me confined inside that
mirror right now instead of Fugo,
I'd want you to make the very same call.
Sorry, but with all due respect...
That's just bullshit!
Fugo is in serious danger, but
that doesn't mean it's all over.
It's our duty to bring him
back safely. But first,
we have to find out how this guy's attacking
us, or we might as well pack it in.
Wrong!
If you think this is bad, wait
till all three of us are taken out!
Again!
We are leaving! Now! I won't!
Finding Fugo, and taking
this guy down's the plan.
Trust me, none of us
will be safe otherwise.
I outrank your stupid ass, you
parvenu prick, so what I say goes!
You still refusing my order?
It's your funeral!
You had better be prepared
to not survive this fight!
I'll ask you once more.
What was your team hoping
to find here in Pompeii?
I'll never tell a scum like you. That so.
What a shame.
But they're still your two friends.
I'm sure one of them could be
persuaded into spilling their guts.
Which makes you worthless!
Every time I close my eyes.
Wake up feeling so horny.
I can't get you out of my mind.
Since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
I need your body.
You got my time.
Yeah, whatever you want.
I will give it, baby.
I need your body.
You won't be sorry.
You got my body.
You got my mind.
I know what I want to do is
freak you, what must I say,
what must I do,
to show how much I'm going to freak you,
what must I say, what must I do,
to show how much I'm going to freak you.
Thank you.